so I'm probably gonna be dealing with
this event that happened well I was
staying in community and I'll be dealing
with it for weeks to learn what I'm
supposed to learn out of it but this
woman Oh aye she's here to teach me
something I know that I can be grateful
for that
but it's it's also like the difference
I'm gonna read some emails she wrote me
an email like less than five hours after
it happened
that is a very like if you hadn't been
part of the interaction wouldn't know
how much of like an evil person she
comes off as when she's angry and in a
moment and says malicious things and no
one else but like she can control
herself when she's writing an email or
when she's interacting in public just
it's just which makes me worry so much
more my name is short me this email when
I came up it was just to talk to you so
we could work out a better arrangement I
felt hurt when you just laughed at me
and said you couldn't do anything I hope
that you will consider the option of
talking instead of just instead of just
yourself gossiping to other people and
refusing to talk with me you gossip to a
lot of people and I didn't stop
referring to her last incident this
community has in part done well because
people do talked with each other not
just laugh and refused which is quite
hurtful intermediaries are busy and if
you want that you should be willing to
pay for them them for their time
I've not talked to this woman's just
Nestle know about the intermediaries
accept them we weren't yelling at each
other I was like go talk to anyone else
don't talk to me but it seems better
less expensive and demanding for us to
calm down and talk with each other so I
hope you can consider that more direct
option like that's a totally ok email if
the interaction hadn't occurred five
hours before like I would look like a
crazy person for being like this email
is over-the-top except the pain for a
part but it's like right right so I
didn't write back right away because I
was stayed there and so this is what I
wrote back I wrote it last night and
then I slept on it and I still felt it
needed to be sent this morning so I have
tried to accommodate your request and I
tried my best to be as quiet as possible
I told my kids walk softly every five
minutes at least
and we both took off our shoes every
time we entered
if only briefly although we were not
able to this visit I have accommodated
gern app several times in the past I
even kept the last incident and all the
interactions since to a handful of
people
none of these are things you are
entitled to I was doing you a favor and
so was my kid you haven't you feel
entitled to have your own way you feel
entitled to have your own way if someone
is not giving you everything you ask for
and exactly the way you want you get
angry and over-the-top ridiculously
maliciously so you think you are more
important than other people especially
me you think you are more entitled to be
in people I was staying at apartment
then the person they asked to stay there
I asked you to leave 30 times attempted
to close the door at least five times
and told you you were trespassing
it took me physically removing you from
the doorway after ten minutes of this
for the interaction to end I honestly do
not know what to do with that except
laughs a woman with decades of
experience on me cannot maintain her
temper or remove herself when she's
clearly shouldn't be from where she
clearly shouldn't be but once my
seven-year-old to somehow control her
joyful body she did a much better job
than you did for the record it is not my
decibels we created the decibels we
create but the hatred you feel for us
that is the problem it just isn't my
problem hate me or don't hate my kid or
don't it doesn't affect me hating you
would it just isn't worth your worth the
energy you are a deeply unhappy woman
who seems to want to destroy communities
wherever you go you have a reputation
for such things it makes me sad for you
how deeply you must be hurting to be to
seek out other people to try to make
miserable I'm not playing
I have many better and more important
things to do with my time on this planet
I like myself too much to put up with
such treatment you do not know the first
thing about interacting with fellow
human beings that has been made apparent
very apparent by our two different
interactions and the countless ones in
between so from now on you do not get to
make requests of me
any communication you have for me that
you want me to consider is going to need
to go through a third party and you're
right they should be compensated for
their time and so should I if you want
me to vacate the place we are staying in
at any point on future visits then you
will need to pay the rent of $10 an hour
to me plus $10 per commune
okay Shinto whichever third party you
end up dealing through still I will not
be obligated to accommodate but I will
consider it if it does not come through
someone else who has been compensated
for that time I will not even consider
it I will be polite so that we do not
create tension for the community
I will not however keep this story to
myself it is not gossip it is a warning
to the kind of person you are when
nobody else is watching I give you one
time for it to be more of a secret this
is not an incident it is a pattern and I
will not keep silent process already
knows about it if you do not want people
to know about the horrible way you
interact with me
stop interacting with me and then she
responded again totally benignly because
in writing she can control herself
Jubilee thank you for writing which
person in process did you talk with so
far or in poor persons did you give the
impression that you did not get angry
when provoked no no I did not that was
definitely not the impression I gave
Mikey the exact opposite impression of
that PS I don't hate you I was trying to
get you to make accommodations not one
is just you there you two there but
regarding having guests children over
she just changes every thirty seconds or
I would or I would have if communica
communicating about that would have been
possible Thanks maybe eventually so
that's the next thing and she sounded
cookie tonight and I signed up for
dinner already so it should be a fun a
fake politeness option I have to figure
out how to not have negative emotions in
my body when I'm around her and what
better way than being around her she is
here to teach me she is I don't know
what that it quite is yet but I it keeps
coming in and a part of it was that last
time I did get process involved and
tried to have a conflict resolution
which was not successful because they
couldn't sit down with her and actually
she wanted me to change only all me like
yes let's sit down and tell Jubilee how
wrong she is that's a great idea I would
love to do that and I wanted to sit down
and see each other's side person has
been in but like there's that learning
that
like there are people who just are
poison for community and the biggest
poison is that there's 90 percent of the
people there that don't even know that
I've had like a tiny interaction but
have not seen the viciousness that comes
out of her when she's alone no one's
been in the scene and she feels superior
to somebody she feels like she has more
power over them and no I kept it quiet
last time That's not me
I'm not like I get that you didn't know
that last time then you kind of figured
that out hey if you don't have
interactions with me because how I
process is talking to everyone that come
across including YouTube it looks like
I'm not giving her name but
but anyway it was for me to know that I
did I emailed her myself to say I'm
never pretty much talking to you again
directly I'm gonna she emailed me back
twice right away yeah 7:30 and then 751
so 20 minutes later but hey she hasn't
since then so good on her she chose the
interactions between time it was very it
was made quite clear through process she
was not to talk to me was not to
communicate with me and she would still
be like whatever anyone else was around
the one time she almost had another
encounter because she knew some hope my
I was gonna write her a letter instead
of doing it I was like I'm not writing
this woman with more ammo like I'm not
explaining my side and her impact she's
had on me because she doesn't care she
all she cares about is how does this
affect me and can I get my way and it
has to be exactly my way I'm like I
tried I was trying to be a good neighbor
I was trying to I get how hard it is to
not be able to nap I get how loud my kid
can be I was trying you're not entitled
to me trying it was a favor and yep you
burn that bridge
yeah like bombed it these heal no need
to watch them if you don't want to hear
about the only drama in my life my life
is very drama-free that's why I'm able
to deal with the world's drama but this
is part of that there's something here
that's here to teach me this woman is in
my path in my community for a reason and
it's for my learning and I'm sure I'm in
her life for a reason too but that's up
to her to learn so
bless her bless her bless her bless her
all right